

CONTACT

• Cheboksary, Russia

+7 906 385 9821

vasiljevdenis@bk.ru

in <u>www.linkedin.com/in/vasiljev</u> <u>denis</u>

vasiljevdenis.github.io

SKILLS

HTML/CSS (Flexbox, Sass, LESS)

lavaScript

React/TypeScript

Node.js

HOBBIES

Reading books

Street Workout

Travellino

OTHER

Date of birth: 28.10.1995

Experience: 1 year

Languages: Russian (Native speaker)

English (Intermediate)

DENIS VASILEV

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

Since 2007 I have fond of IT. At first I was engaged in system administration and computer repair. Since 2009 I started to be interested in web technologies as well as graphic design. From 2010 to 2014 I periodically worked as a computer master (in particular, at my school during my studies).

The greatest interest in web programming appeared in 2020, and already in 2021 I started working in the field of freelance website development.

JOB EXPERIENCE

2021 – present time

Freelance

Ò

WEB DEVELOPER

Website development, layout and revision in source code and on CMS. Last projects:

agrochat.net

fincity-official.ru

kristinakvitko.com

Holy Trinity

monastery in

Cheboksary

2018 - 2022

DEACON

Church service in monastery.

EDUCATION

Theological . . .

seminary in

Nizhny Novgorod

2016 - 2022

ChSPU in

Cheboksary

2014 - 2016

BACHELOR OF THEOLOGY

Full-time and distance leraning.

BACHELOR OF HISTORY

Two courses.

Electromechanical O

college in

Cheboksary

2012 - 2014

COURSES

Computing, design, databases.